This is just what I needed.
这正是我所需要的.
It is a lovely park,isn't it?
真是个漂亮的公园,是吧?
So tell me,Simon,how did you wind up here, a restaurant manager in Boston?
So Simon, 告诉我你是怎么成为Boston这家饭店的餐厅经理的?
Ah!Well,that's a bit of a puzzle to me,as well.
Ah! Well, 这对我来讲也有点儿像个迷.
Was your training in restaurants?
你受过餐厅管理方面的训练吗?
Oh no!After primary and secondary schools I went to university.
Oh no! 读完小学和中学后我上了大学.
Manchester.Modern languages.
Manchester. 学现代语言.
That's a lot of tests.
那要有很多的考试.
Oh yes,I passed all kinds of exams.
Oh yes, 我通过了各种各样的考试.
I was never any good at taking tests.
我考试向来不好.
I barely got through elementary school.
勉勉强强才读完小学(elementary school).
High school was worse.
高中更糟.
And it was years before I went to college.
过了好多年才上大学.
And I didn't do very well there either,I'm afraid.
而且大学也念得不怎么好.
Oh,I did well,but there was something missing.
Oh, 我学的还不错, 但有些东西没学到.
At the end of the day,I wanted experience that was...
学业完成后, 我想要一点儿经验,那种……
Hands-on.
实践经验.
Exactly.
一点儿不错.
Find out the way it works in the real world.
想了解现实世界是怎样的.
Yes.
So you got a job!
所以你找了份工作?
NO.I went back to business school for management studies.
不, 我回到商学院学习管理.
More tests!
更多的考试!